  export const conheciementosGerais = [
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Electronic%20music%20producer%20Kygo%27s%20popularity%20skyrocketed%20after%20a%20certain%20remix.%20Which%20song%20did%20he%20remix%3F",
"correct_answer": "Ed%20Sheeran%20-%20I%20See%20Fire",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Marvin%20Gaye%20-%20Sexual%20Healing",
"Coldplay%20-%20Midnight",
"a-ha%20-%20Take%20On%20Me"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20type%20of%20dog%20is%20%27Handsome%20Dan%27%2C%20the%20mascot%20of%20Yale%20University%3F",
"correct_answer": "Bulldog",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Yorkshire%20Terrier",
"Boxer",
"Pug"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20airspeed%20velocity%20of%20an%20unladen%20swallow%3F",
"correct_answer": "24%20MPH",
"incorrect_answers": [
"15%20MPH",
"20%20MPH",
"200%20MPH"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "The%20words%20%22bungalow%22%20and%20%22shampoo%22%20originate%20from%20the%20languages%20of%20which%20country%3F",
"correct_answer": "India",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Papua%20New%20Guinea",
"Ethiopia",
"China"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "When%20was%20%22YouTube%22%20founded%3F",
"correct_answer": "February%2014%2C%202005",
"incorrect_answers": [
"May%2022%2C%202004",
"September%2012%2C%202005",
"July%2019%2C%202009"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Before%20the%2019th%20Century%2C%20the%20%22Living%20Room%22%20was%20originally%20called%20the...",
"correct_answer": "Parlor",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Open%20Room",
"Sitting%20Room",
"Loft"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20year%20was%20Queen%20Elizabeth%20II%20born%3F",
"correct_answer": "1926",
"incorrect_answers": [
"1923",
"1929",
"1930"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20is%20not%20another%20name%20for%20the%20eggplant%3F",
"correct_answer": "Potimarron",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Brinjal",
"Guinea%20Squash",
"Melongene"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20chemicals%20are%20found%20in%20eggplant%20seeds%3F",
"correct_answer": "Nicotine",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Mescaline",
"Cyanide",
"Psilocybin"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Sciophobia%20is%20the%20fear%20of%20what%3F",
"correct_answer": "Shadows",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Eating",
"Bright%20lights",
"Transportation"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20is%20an%20existing%20family%20in%20%22The%20Sims%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "The%20Goth%20Family",
"incorrect_answers": [
"The%20Family",
"The%20Simoleon%20Family",
"The%20Proud%20Family"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20banks%20are%20NOT%20authorized%20to%20issue%20currency%20notes%20in%20Hong%20Kong%3F",
"correct_answer": "OCBC",
"incorrect_answers": [
"HSBC",
"Standard%20Chartered",
"Bank%20of%20China"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20romanized%20Korean%20word%20for%20%22heart%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Simjang",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Aejeong",
"Jeongsin",
"Segseu"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20romanized%20Arabic%20word%20for%20%22moon%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Qamar",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Najma",
"Kawkab",
"Shams"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20musician%20has%20collaborated%20with%20American%20producer%20Porter%20Robinson%20and%20released%20the%202016%20song%20%22Shelter%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Madeon",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Mat%20Zo",
"deadmau5",
"Zedd"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "The%20Swedish%20word%20%22Grunka%22%20means%20what%20in%20English%3F",
"correct_answer": "Thing",
"incorrect_answers": [
"People",
"Place",
"Pineapple"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Disney%27s%20Haunted%20Mansion%20is%20home%20to%20a%20trio%20of%20Hitchhiking%20Ghosts.%20Which%20of%20these%20is%20NOT%20one%20of%20them%3F",
"correct_answer": "Harry",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Gus",
"Phineas",
"Ezra"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "How%20long%20did%20it%20take%20the%20motorized%20window%20washers%20of%20the%20original%20World%20Trade%20Center%20to%20clean%20the%20entire%20exterior%20of%20the%20building%3F",
"correct_answer": "1%20Month",
"incorrect_answers": [
"3%20Weeks",
"1%20Week",
"2%20Months"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20languages%20does%20NOT%20use%20gender%20as%20a%20part%20of%20its%20grammar%3F",
"correct_answer": "Turkish",
"incorrect_answers": [
"German",
"Danish",
"Polish"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20one%20of%20these%20Swedish%20companies%20was%20founded%20in%201943%3F",
"correct_answer": "IKEA",
"incorrect_answers": [
"H%20%26%20M",
"Lindex",
"Clas%20Ohlson"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "How%20many%20calories%20are%20in%20a%20355%20ml%20can%20of%20Pepsi%20Cola%3F",
"correct_answer": "150",
"incorrect_answers": [
"200",
"100",
"155"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "De%20Eemhof%2C%20Port%20Zelande%20and%20Het%20Heijderbos%20are%20holiday%20villas%20owned%20by%20what%20company%3F",
"correct_answer": "Center%20Parcs",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Yelloh%20Village",
"Keycamp",
"Villa%20Plus"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20year%20was%20the%20RoboSapien%20toy%20robot%20released%3F",
"correct_answer": "2004",
"incorrect_answers": [
"2000",
"2001",
"2006"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "According%20to%20Fair%20Works%20Australia%2C%20how%20long%20do%20you%20have%20to%20work%20to%20get%20Long%20Service%20Leave%3F",
"correct_answer": "7%20years",
"incorrect_answers": [
"2%20years",
"8%20years",
"6%20months"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "According%20to%20the%202014-2015%20Australian%20Bureau%20of%20Statistics%2C%20what%20percentage%20of%20Australians%20were%20born%20overseas%3F",
"correct_answer": "28%25",
"incorrect_answers": [
"13%25",
"20%25",
"7%25"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20was%20Bank%20of%20America%20originally%20established%20as%3F",
"correct_answer": "Bank%20of%20Italy",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Bank%20of%20Long%20Island",
"Bank%20of%20Pennsylvania",
"Bank%20of%20Charlotte"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20product%20did%20Nokia%2C%20the%20telecommunications%20company%2C%20originally%20sell%3F",
"correct_answer": "Paper",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Phones",
"Computers",
"Processors"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20does%20the%20Latin%20phrase%20%22Veni%2C%20vidi%2C%20vici%22%20translate%20into%20English%3F",
"correct_answer": "I%20came%2C%20I%20saw%2C%20I%20conquered",
"incorrect_answers": [
"See%20no%20evil%2C%20hear%20no%20evil%2C%20speak%20no%20evil",
"Life%2C%20liberty%2C%20and%20happiness",
"Past%2C%20present%2C%20and%20future"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Virtual%20reality%20company%20Oculus%20VR%20lost%20which%20of%20it%27s%20co-founders%20in%20a%20freak%20car%20accident%20in%202013%3F",
"correct_answer": "Andrew%20Scott%20Reisse",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Nate%20Mitchell",
"Jack%20McCauley",
"Palmer%20Luckey"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Who%20founded%20the%20Khan%20Academy%3F",
"correct_answer": "Sal%20Khan",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Ben%20Khan",
"Kitt%20Khan",
"Adel%20Khan"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20flight%20systems%2C%20what%20does%20the%20initialism%20%22TCAS%22%20stand%20for%3F",
"correct_answer": "Traffic%20Collision%20Avoidance%20System",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Traffic%20Communication%20Alert%20System",
"Traffic%20Configuration%20Alignment%20System",
"Traffic%20Call-sign%20Abbreviation%20System"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "If%20someone%20said%20%22you%20are%20olid%22%2C%20what%20would%20they%20mean%3F",
"correct_answer": "You%20smell%20extremely%20unpleasant.",
"incorrect_answers": [
"You%20are%20out%20of%20shape%2Fweak.",
"Your%20appearance%20is%20repulsive.",
"You%20are%20incomprehensible%2Fan%20idiot."
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Named%20after%20the%20mallow%20flower%2C%20mauve%20is%20a%20shade%20of%20what%3F",
"correct_answer": "Purple",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Red",
"Brown",
"Pink"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Chartreuse%20is%20a%20color%20between%20yellow%20and%20what%3F",
"correct_answer": "Green",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Red",
"Black",
"Purple"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Originally%20another%20word%20for%20poppy%2C%20coquelicot%20is%20a%20shade%20of%20what%3F",
"correct_answer": "Red",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Green",
"Blue",
"Pink"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Nephelococcygia%20is%20the%20practice%20of%20doing%20what%3F",
"correct_answer": "Finding%20shapes%20in%20clouds",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Sleeping%20with%20your%20eyes%20open",
"Breaking%20glass%20with%20your%20voice",
"Swimming%20in%20freezing%20water"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "The%20Quadrangularis%20Reversum%20is%20best%20described%20as%20which%20of%20the%20following%3F",
"correct_answer": "A%20percussion%20instrument",
"incorrect_answers": [
"A%20building%20in%20Oxford%20University",
"A%20chess%20move",
"A%20geometric%20theorem"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Where%20is%20Apple%20Inc.%20headquartered%3F",
"correct_answer": "Cupertino%2C%20California",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Redwood%20City%2C%20California",
"Redmond%2C%20Washington",
"Santa%20Monica%2C%20CA"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20church%27s%20interior%20in%20Vatican%20City%20was%20designed%20in%201503%20by%20renaissance%20architects%20including%20Bramante%2C%20Michelangelo%20and%20Bernini%3F",
"correct_answer": "St.%20Peter%27s%20Basilica",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Catania%20Cathedral",
"St.%20Mark%E2%80%99s%20Basilica",
"The%20Duomo%20of%20Florence"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "If%20you%20planted%20the%20seeds%20of%20Quercus%20robur%2C%20what%20would%20grow%3F",
"correct_answer": "Trees",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Grains",
"Vegetables",
"Flowers"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Located%20in%20Chile%2C%20El%20Teniente%20is%20the%20world%27s%20largest%20underground%20mine%20for%20what%20metal%3F",
"correct_answer": "Copper",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Iron",
"Nickel",
"Silver"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "How%20many%20notes%20are%20there%20on%20a%20standard%20grand%20piano%3F",
"correct_answer": "88",
"incorrect_answers": [
"98",
"108",
"78"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20the%20MMO%20RPG%20%22Realm%20of%20the%20Mad%20God%22%2C%20what%20dungeon%20is%20widely%20considered%20to%20be%20the%20most%20difficult%3F",
"correct_answer": "The%20Shatter%27s",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Snake%20Pit",
"The%20Tomb%20of%20the%20Acient%27s",
"The%20Puppet%20Master%27s%20Theater"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20weight%20of%20a%20Gold%20Bar%20in%20Fallout%3A%20New%20Vegas%3F",
"correct_answer": "35%20Pounds",
"incorrect_answers": [
"30%20Pounds",
"40%20Pounds",
"32.50%20Pounds"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "The%20word%20%22abulia%22%20means%20which%20of%20the%20following%3F",
"correct_answer": "The%20inability%20to%20make%20decisions",
"incorrect_answers": [
"The%20inability%20to%20stand%20up",
"The%20inability%20to%20concentrate%20on%20anything",
"A%20feverish%20desire%20to%20rip%20one%27s%20clothes%20off"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "The%20word%20%22astasia%22%20means%20which%20of%20the%20following%3F",
"correct_answer": "The%20inability%20to%20stand%20up",
"incorrect_answers": [
"The%20inability%20to%20make%20decisions",
"The%20inability%20to%20concentrate%20on%20anything",
"A%20feverish%20desire%20to%20rip%20one%27s%20clothes%20off"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "The%20word%20%22aprosexia%22%20means%20which%20of%20the%20following%3F",
"correct_answer": "The%20inability%20to%20concentrate%20on%20anything",
"incorrect_answers": [
"The%20inability%20to%20make%20decisions",
"A%20feverish%20desire%20to%20rip%20one%27s%20clothes%20off",
"The%20inability%20to%20stand%20up"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20cities%20does%20NOT%20have%20a%20United%20States%20Minting%20location%3F",
"correct_answer": "St.%20Louis%2C%20MO",
"incorrect_answers": [
"San%20Fransisco%2C%20CA",
"Philidelphia%2C%20PA",
"West%20Point%2C%20NY"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20%20British%20Monarchs%20never%20appeared%20on%20a%20circulated%20pound%20sterling%20coin%3F",
"correct_answer": "Edward%20VIII",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Victoria",
"George%20VI",
"Charles%20II"
]
},
{
"category": "General%20Knowledge",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20%22Resident%20Evil%203%22%2C%20how%20many%20inventory%20slots%20does%20Jill%20have%20at%20the%20start%20of%20the%20game%3F",
"correct_answer": "10",
"incorrect_answers": [
"6",
"8",
"12"
]
}
]